octafind.com 2009-04-10

# OctaFind - Privacy Policy

_As a general rule, OctaFind does not collect any personally identifiable data about our users except in specific instances, such as if you choose to advertise with our service. _

OctaFind provides a number of search related services.  As such, we follow a unified information handling practice and make every effort to disclose our use of information.  This privacy policy is an example of that effort.

**  
What is covered by this privacy policy?**

This privacy policy covers information collected and stored by OctaFind.  Please note that as a search service provider, OctaFind links to third party web sites and may provide search services for third party web sites.  These third party web sites are not covered under this privacy policy and OctaFind is not responsible for the content or information collection policies of such third parties.

**  
Third party banner ads**

OctaFind may use third party companies to serve some or all of its banner advertisements.  As these companies are not part of OctaFind, they are not bound by this privacy policy.  You may find more information about some of these companies and choose to opt out of their information collection mechanisms by visiting the [NAI website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).  The NAI opt-out only covers those web sites which have voluntarily chosen to provide an opt-out mechanism.

**  
What information does OctaFind collect and how is it used?**

OctaFind collects at least three types of distinct data, (1) clickstream, (2) cookie data and (3) contact and personally identifiable information.

(1) _Clickstream data_  
OctaFind collects data about the flow of traffic into, through, and out of our web site.  Clickstream data is not personally identifiable.  OctaFind may share clickstream data with selected third parties.

(2) _Cookies_  
Like many web sites, OctaFind may use cookies to track online behavior information.  The cookies sent by OctaFind are not readable by any third-party sites and do not contain any personally identifiable information.  We may share cookie data with selected third parties.

(3) _Contact information and personally identifiable information_  
OctaFind can only obtain access to your contact or personally identifiable information if you choose to (a) become an advertiser with us, (b) submit a feedback or other form and provide such information, (c) in connection with a contest or special promotion.  Contact information provided to OctaFind may from time to time be shared with select third parties who wish to provide special promotions in conjunction with the OctaFind service.  Users may opt out of this type of disclosure at any time by contacting OctaFind.

**  
Is the data you provide to OctaFind stored securely?**

We have taken measures to ensure the security of your personal information.  However, security of data is an ever evolving field.  As such, please treat any communication with OctaFind as non-confidential and do not submit confidential information through our feedback forms or other mechanisms.

**  
How do I contact OctaFind if I have a question about this privacy policy or any information about me stored or collected by OctaFind?**

If you have questions about this privacy policy or about our collection of information, you may contact us at:

OctaFind  
ATTN:  Privacy Policy Coordinator  
100 Adams Blvd.  
Farmingdale, NY 11735  
E-mail:  Use contact form

This policy may be periodically revised at the discretion of OctaFind.  You are responsible for notifying us within 14 days if you do not agree with any changes to this policy and request to have any personally identifiable information stored at OctaFind deleted.  Failure to notify us within 14 days signals your agreement with the revised privacy policy.

This privacy policy was last updated on **April 29, 2002.   ** Previous to last revision on **July 18, 2001**.
